dvhardware.net 2017-08-24

# DV Hardware - Privacy policy

---|---  
  
**Privacy Policy**  
DV Hardware has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our website. All personal information that you entrust to DV Hardware by creating a user account, publishing comments, submitting to a newsletter, participating in one of our contests or any other action will be treated confidentially. Your information is safe with us and will not be sold to third parties. 

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, the time you visited our site and which pages you requested from our server. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as user accounts. 

We also use third party advertisements on DV Hardware to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited. Google for instance may use this data to serve ads based on your preferences, but it's possible to opt out [over here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts. 

**Links**  
DV Hardware contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for either the content or privacy practices of these sites. 

If you have questions about our privacy policy, contact us by e-mailing [thomas.dm@dvhardware.net](mailto:thomas.dm@dvhardware.net)

All logos and trademarks in this site are property of their respective owner.  
The comments are property of their posters, all the rest © 2002 by DarkVision Hardware
